

NGUYỄN NGỌC QUÌNH

Teacher

About Me

I am Nguyen Ngoc Quynh, I had a little experiences in education but I really really love this field. I have the ability to convey information well and I want to explain my understanding to everyone.

So I am finding out an oppotunity to become a teacher.

ť



Education

University of Greenwich

Bachelor of Information Technology 2018 - 2022

Skills

- Explaination Skills
- Creativity
- Comprehend Skills
- Laborious
- Critical Thinking
- Teamwork

Experiences

Teaching Assistant

2018-2022

During my University process, I have the opportunity to work as a teaching assistant for a private home education center. At this time, I am assigned responsibilities such as:

- Arrange and maintain classroom order.
- · Check out student's homeworks.
- Explain and guide students in doing exercises.
- Check out and correct exercises.

FPT Software 2021

Front-end Intern

I had a 2-month internship at the company when I was in my 3rd year majoring in IT. Here, I learned from experience as:

- Teamwork through Trello
- Daily report with Google Meet
- Learn Information Security skills
- Clone education website by HTML, CSS JS

FPT Retail (FRT)

2022-2024

Front-end Developer

I had worked in the company over 2 years when graduated. In this company, I have been trained and implemented web programming skills such as:

- Stored code via Git, Github
- Analyze, divide layout, estimate deadline when receiving tasks
- Excute web interface programming: landing, theme, system, e-commercial pages,...
- Enhanced UI/UX
- Fix bugs
- Proficient in using HTML, CSS, Javascript and some libraries or framework as JQuery, Bootstraps, ReactJS,...
- Proficient in working with SCSS, LESS, and SASS.
- Proficient in using teamwork tools such as Git, GitLab, Jira, Trello, mail,...
- Work according to Agile / Scrum models

Expertises

- English communication well
- Basic Japanese, Korean
- Proficient in Office Technology: Word, Excel,
 PowerPoint, Mail, ...